ДОПОЛНЕНИЕ
A
An educated person is a man who _______a lot about many things
	Ответ: knows

At 8 o’clock I leave home and go ___ school
	to 

A couple of years ago I _______ to become a doctor
	wanted 

I
I think the best way to ___ to know and understand people is to meet them in their own homes
	Ответ: get
I may ____ to bed very late because sometimes I watch television till late in the evening
	Ответ: go

If we caught cold and are ___ high temperature, we must go to the policlinic
	running 

If we are _______ of travelling, we see and learn a lot of things that we can never see or learn at home
	fond 

I lay on the examination couch and the doctor _______my abdomen
	palpated

I ______ that point yet.  
	haven’t considered

I always remember the proverb: “Early to bed and early to _______ makes a man healthy wealthy and wise.”
	rise 

I usually get __ at 7 o’clock in the morning
	up 

I help my mother about the house if she _______my help
	needs

In the USA there is such youth organizations __ a Young Republican Federation
	as

I have supper and if the weather ___ not good I stay at home
	is

It’s always interesting to discover new things, to listen ___ different musical rhythms
	to

H
He _______ to sit down in a chair and to strip to the waist
	offered 

He always tries to _______, find out, discover more about the world around him
	learn 

J
Jane ______ suddenly that there was a letter attached to the painting.
	had found
	has found


L
Last time my temperature ____ 37,9
	was 

M
Mary isn’t at home. She ______ to work
	Ответ: has gone
More and more women nowadays _______ jobs
	Ответ: have
My house is a typical Russian ___
	Ответ: house

N
Nowadays it has more rights than before and is free to demonstrate itself as it _______
	wants 

O
One more problem also exists as far as teenagers ___ because they also belong to youth
	Ответ: go

Of course speaking and _______ in a foreign language is a difficult process
	writing 

S
Some young people work in their church organizations: help elderly people or work _______ hospitals
	in

Since then I ______ my job several time.
	have changed

T
They ______ in construction business for 5 years.
	Ответ: have been
This _______ that both countries have a large number of “single parent families”
	Ответ: means
To be successful in studies _______ must work hard
	Ответ: one

The typical British family has a car, a colour TV set, a washing machine, and a cat or dog as _______
	well

There __ all conditions for young people in Russia in which they can realize themselves
	are 

The role of foreign languages is also _______ today
	increasing 

Thanks to the knowledge of foreign languages a person can ___ books
	read 

The doctor wrote out a prescription for some _______: pills, powder, drops, and mixture
	medicines 

The typical family _______ a father, a mother and two children
	has

W
When you leave school the time to choose your future profession has _______
	Ответ: come
When people come to a big city they spend their time visiting museums and ___ galleries
	Ответ: b. culture  

When a problem comes, we must _______ ready to solve it
	be

Y
You should find out all you _______ about any job which interests you
	Ответ: can

You also need to think about what you _______ like to do
	would

“You ______ your hair”, he cried.
	have dyed

_______a good doctor you must be patient, easygoing and kind
	To become


ВЫБОРКА

A) Organizing means arranging and allocating work
B) Marketing are used to create the customer, to keep the customer and to satisfy the customer
	Ответ: А - да, В - нет

A) Marketing is an integrated process
B) Marketing be an integrated process
	Ответ: А - да, В - нет

A) The populations of the USA has stopped growing
B) Family life in the west has changed a lot over the 20-th century
	Ответ: А - нет, В - да

A) Organizing is the process of arranging and allocating work,
B) Management comprises planning, organizing, staffing, leading, and controlling a firm.
	Ответ: А - да, В - да

A) A couple of years ago I had wanted to become a doctor
B) A couple of years ago I wanted to become a doctor
	Ответ: А - нет, В - да

A) If scarcity is absent, there is no economic problem
B) If scarcity been absent, there is no economic problem
	Ответ: А - да, В - нет // НЕВЕРНЫЙ

A) Information science should not be confused with information theory
B) When a question comes, we must be ready to solve it
	Ответ: А - да, В - да

A) Management is often included as a factor of production
B) Management are often included as a factor of production
	А - да, В - нет

A) Psychological knowledges is applied to various spheres of human activity
B) Psychological knowledge is applied to various spheres of human activity
	А - нет, В - да

A) Their parents is usually home by 6 o’clock
B) Their children are in the garden playing football
	А - нет, В - да

A) The importance of foreign languages has increased today
B) They try to understand the role of mental functions
	А - да, В - да

A) Information science is often considered a branch of computer science
B) Information science be often considered a branch of
	А - да, В - нет

A) If scarcity has absent, there is no economic problem
B) Marketings is used to create the customer, to keep the customer and to satisfy the customer
	А - нет, В - нет

A) Directors and managers has the power and responsibility to make decisions
B) Directors and managers have the power and responsibility to make decisions
	А - нет, В - да

A) Legal code are a system of rules, usually enforced through a set of institutions
B) You also need to think what you would like to do
	А - нет, В - да

A) There is many reasons why people study foreign languages
B) There are many reasons why people study foreign languages
	А - нет, В - да

A) Modern jurisprudence has began in the 18th century
B) Modern jurisprudence began in the 18th century
	А - нет, В - да

A) To become a good doctor you must to be patient, easygoing and kind
B) To become a good doctor you must be patient, easygoing and kind
	А - нет, В - да

A) You should find out all you can about your future job
B) You also need to think what you would like to do
	А - да, B - да

A) When a problem comes, we must be ready to solve it
B) When a problem comes, we must to be ready to solve it
	А - да, В - нет

A) Law is a systems of rules
B) They are in the garden playing football
	А - нет, В - нет

A) Marketing concept is used to create the customer
B) The use of foreign languages is also increasing today
	А - да, В - да

A) Psychology is an academic and applied discipline
B) Psychology study such phenomena as perception, cognition, attention, emotion
	А - да, В - нет

A) Most holiday-makers take a camera with them
B) Most holiday-makers takes a camera with them
	А - да, В - нет

Верна ли грамматическая конструкция в данных предложениях?    A) A couple of years ago I had wanted to become a doctor     B) The population of the USA has stopped growing
	А - нет, В - да

Верна ли грамматическая конструкция в данных предложениях?     A) The populations of the USA has stopped growing      B) Family life in the west has changed a lot over the 20-th century
	А - нет, В - да

Верна ли грамматическая конструкция в данных предложениях?   A) Legal code are a system of rules, usually enforced through a set of institutions        B) You also need to think what you would like to do
	А - нет, В - да
	




